# NOUR **KHALAYLE**

#### A GRADUATE ENGINEER SOFTWARE TESTER

Hey, I'm Nour, 20 years old Graduated from Smart Academy College QA Engineer (manual & automation). ISTQB certification. Ability to learn quickly, often in high-pressure situations to fully understand a new product, platform, or any mixture of the two, I have many projects on the server, and I know a lot of programming languages



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nour-khalayle-799753224/

## **PROJECTS**

#### **The First Project:**

It was in MTM Test real software and websites and write test documents.

#### **The Second Project:**

It was in the JIRA Group project in Jira, checking test status, writing STP, STD documents, and doing tests for different sites.



#### My Website:

https://nooraldenchating.000webhostapp.com/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 15/3 - 27/3 Smart Group with Carbyne Company

System test Volunteer project with Carbyne Company, 991 system for an emergency with college.

# 7/2021 - Present, Freelancer Tester, UTest

Test software or websites offered on UTEST.

#### 4/2019 - Present, Selling Projects, Upwork

Programming websites and selling personal projects, Website design

# 2018 - 2019 food preparation, Mcdonal'z, Herzliya

Different work, whether in the kitchen or outside

## CONTACT



+972522799242



nooralden.12.n@gmail.com



driver's license: B. C1

# **EDUCATION**

March 2021 - October 2021

Smart College, Tel-Aviv

MANUAL SOFTWARE TESTER COURSE MTM & JIRA TESTING DOCUMENTS STP STD STR

Quality assurance engineer certificate

2020 - 2021

## **AL-Qasemi of Engineering & Science**

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 

A full year of programming languages, website building, and language algorithms, in addition to the database language

#### COURSES

- CYBER and information security course(96)
- Linux System Administrator(85)
- Tester Automation Software Selenium(86)
- OOP JAVA

## 2014 - 2017

**Diploma(Full Units), HIGH SCHOOL ATID, Taibe** Certificate of graduation full units

# SKILLS

